Hello hi my friends practice
I pray that everyone is happy
and I want to thank
my friends who
supported me so much, gave me so much love and liked this video so much
my previous video so
today we will discuss
about comprehensive insurance in case of
accidents before that I
would like to say that please like this video
subscribe and tell as many people as you can
and please remember me in your prayers so this is
our first part of our tripath series
and today we will discuss
comprehensive insurance it was
about first party insurance
and now the most important and goes this
comprehensive insurance or first
insurance understand for example third
party insurance which is ₹100
so congress minutes call it
friends what happens on the railway line
if you are travelling in a vehicle and there was a
mistake on the other side
and your vehicle gets destroyed and you
also get injured
and the vehicle of the person in front also gets damaged
his driver and passenger also get
damaged these are missionaries right
first  Same as what was told in the above part,
Samson, the only difference is that who are you, then the
insurance company will
say okay,
we will pay for the repairing of the car of the person in front of me and
we will also provide a course for repairing your car,
here it will be made to your mind that
forget the car in front,
how much will the company pay for your car,
we will also have to pay some money from our pocket,
now what happens in comprehensive insurance is
that if any smart of the meter gets
damaged then the insurance company will
give us hundred percent money to get it repaired
and if there is a plastic part, let's say
50,000, the
company will write off the insurance in Ajay,
if I have another thing like Raw Amrit of ₹100,
it is a jar or it is worth 10,000, then it will write off the insurance,
so now if
we meet with an accident, if the tyre bursts or gets
damaged, then the insurance company will pay
50% and what happens to you is either
general comprehensive
insurance
or simple  Comprehensive insurance is
more like here in India we say
first party normal third party
insurance
now the question arises
what is comprehensive insurance
now say conference insurance I have just hit my
car with conference in
joints, should
I get the full amount or not
but it does not happen like this today there is the
cost of delivery or else Rafale is
required, file is required from every insurance company there are
different rates for them you will have to
ask your insurance company sir
or else when you take internet
you have to inquire on time
and 1 green chilli there is different system of intercourse
according to the line so
according to each company if you
take normal conference then you have to take
advance on what you get in normal,
I have edited features on the cigarette on top of that
you have additional features benefits so
I don't what is it,
we will talk about it now, right now the biggest
advance is a lot but Amazon has done
looking at the first wrestler that we have to take, there is
dowry in conference insurance from them also  There were
two
bomb blasts there along with that, subscribe to the plastic channel
after seeing the unnecessary file charges and whenever the
car is parked near job accident support, if there is any
here also then the car will
always have to be taken to the garage from there
depending on the open loop line gain and you know
in sodium Gandhi Advance Sexual Advanced it is
different what your charges will be
and you get extra benefit,
we are after this depression plastic
blouse and all that
insurance company ltd, so let's
come friends, how much extra money will it cost to take
this zero depression plan in the finance ministry, so
understand that it will cost you two hundred
rupees for low pressure backward, consider it
almost raw, you will have to subscribe for this, it is
260,
so for cooperative insurance you will have to pay two hundred
rupees and for this youth
till 30, how much did I get, for 230, how much did I get, that is Rs. 20, so
along with that it was Rs.
9000, which is a
little up and down,
estimate according to Alwar company  It doesn't happen, so
friends, this is where
our segment ends.
In Mexico, we will talk
about I Don't and there are
different I Don't and what are its features. So,
you should keep getting this kind of information
and to encourage us too, please press the
subscribe button and the bell
icon. Have a pizza and your life
will change. Thank you.